<?xml version='1.0'?>
<feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'>
	<title>www.savjee.be</title>
	<link href='http://www.savjee.be/'/>
	<link type='application/atom+xml' rel='self' href='http://www.savjee.be/atom.xml'/>
	<updated>2014-07-14T22:44:56-07:00</updated>
	<id>http://www.savjee.be/</id>

	<author>
		<name>Xavier Decuyper</name>
		<email>xavier.decuyper@gmail.com</email>
	</author>

	
	<entry>
		<title>Jekyll Powered Blog on Github</title>
		<link type='text/html' href='http://www.savjee.be/2014/Jekyll-Powered-Blog-on-Github/'/>
		<id>http://www.savjee.be/2014/Jekyll-Powered-Blog-on-Github/</id>
		<updated>2014-07-12T00:00:00-07:00</updated>

		<author>
			<name>Xavier Decuyper</name>
			<uri>http://www.savjee.be/</uri>
		</author>

		<content type='html'>&lt;p&gt;Before I wrote this article, I asked myself why I choose to host my blog on Github. However, I cannot find a satisfying reason to convince everyone. There are so many choices there. For instance, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wordpress.com&quot;&gt;Wordpress.com&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.blogger.com/&quot;&gt;Blogger&lt;/a&gt; are two free good blogging platforms. If you prefer Markdown editing, &lt;a href=&quot;https://ghost.org/&quot;&gt;Ghost&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://logdown.com/&quot;&gt;Logdown&lt;/a&gt; provide good solutions for editors. There is no sliver bullet from Jekyll powered Blog. So, who is the potential user of Jekyll powered Blog on Github?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, you have some basic idea of web programming and Markdown editing. Second, you only blog on some specific machines. Third and most importantly, &lt;em&gt;you want to control every code on your blog&lt;/em&gt;. If you meet all of those, you should go through this article and get some ideas of Jekyll powered blog.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
	</entry>
  
	<entry>
		<title>Poor Man Profiler - knowing CPU usage</title>
		<link type='text/html' href='http://www.savjee.be/2014/Poor-Man-Profiler/'/>
		<id>http://www.savjee.be/2014/Poor-Man-Profiler/</id>
		<updated>2014-06-10T00:00:00-07:00</updated>

		<author>
			<name>Xavier Decuyper</name>
			<uri>http://www.savjee.be/</uri>
		</author>

		<content type='html'>&lt;p&gt;We usually face a situation that we don’t know which parts in the program use more CPU time. Therefore, there are so many application profiler out there. For instance, &lt;a href=&quot;http://oprofile.sourceforge.net/news/&quot;&gt;Oprofile&lt;/a&gt; is a famous profiler, which could be used to monitor the application. &lt;a href=&quot;http://poormansprofiler.org/&quot;&gt;Poor Man Profiler&lt;/a&gt;, however, could further provide the benefit of tracking the complete stack and profiling all threads of to the same process.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
	</entry>
  
</feed>